[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The vicuna, a South American animal, is a close relative of this other animal.", "correct_answer": "Llama", "incorrect_answers": ["Iguana", "Tarantula", "Chinchilla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Right and gray whales have been over-fished almost to extinction. Which of the following is a gray or right whale?", "correct_answer": "Bowhead whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue whale", "Sperm whale", "Narwhal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bug comes out of the human body of Kim Jong Il at the end of the movie Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "cockroach", "incorrect_answers": ["spider", "gnat", "beetle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wolf pups are usually born with irises of this color, which changes with time.", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Golden", "Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Italy is a major world exporter of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Sport and luxury vehicles", "Motor vehicles", "Fashion items"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Latin word for apple is malus, which is considered to be derived from the word malum. What does malum mean?", "correct_answer": "Evil", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Sweet", "Pain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Little Miss sunshine, Uncle Frank considers himself to be Americas top scholar on which famous author?", "correct_answer": "Proust", "incorrect_answers": ["Dickens", "Camus", "Kafka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the beach drug dealers connection in the movie Fletch?", "correct_answer": "Chief Jerry Karlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Ted Underhill", "Frank Walker", "Dr. Joseph Dolan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the name of the company that manufactures several first aid remedies?", "correct_answer": "Johnson and Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Proctor and Gamble", "Clark and Lewis", "Black and Decker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first commander of a nuclear submarine?", "correct_answer": "Eugene P. Wilkerson", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Clarke", "Lewis Groton", "Melvin Carver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By the end of the 16th century, a country called Commonwealth of Both Nations covered almost 1 million square kilometers of Europe. Which two countries formed it?", "correct_answer": "Poland and Lithuania", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden and Denmark", "Russia and Ukraine", "Austria and Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1994-2004 television sitcom Friends, which two characters were siblings?", "correct_answer": "Monica and Ross", "incorrect_answers": ["Rachel and Monica", "Ross and Chandler", "Ross and Rachel"]}]